<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sharad Shriram</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Sharad Shriram</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:58:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sharadshriram.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo switch and plans for this blog</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:58:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</guid><description>I have been exploring different static site generators to build my website for a while. The last iteration of this site on https://sharadshriram.github.io was developed on Jekyll where I was tried my hand on understanding the templating language with Jekyll. It was a nice experience where I tried adapting a customized variant of the Read-only theme that was developed by the folks at HTML5up.net.
While I was putting togeher the previous iteration of the site, I had checked out hugo.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</guid><description>My current research interests are broadly in the topics of Human-centered AI, Natural Language Processing, Edge Intelligence, and Data-driven Modelling.
An up-to-date list of publications is available on Google Scholar
2020 P Parag, P Patil, S Shriram, R Sundaresan, H Tyagi, N K. Vaidhiyan. 2020. “Antidote” for CoVID-19 pandemic induced surge in online learning. ACM SIGCOMM Online Networking Education Discussion workshop. PDF 2019 Master Thesis: “A Human-Machine Approach to Preserve Privacy in Image Analysis Crowdsourcing Tasks”, TU Delft (2019).</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am currently working as an internal contributor to the DataCommons project.
Previously, I worked at the Centre for Networked Intelligence at the Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India. I completed my masters in Computer Science with a specialization in Data Science and Technology from the Web Information Systems group, at the Delft University of Technology under the supervision of Prof. Dr. ir. Alessandro Bozzon. During my stay in the Netherlands, I spent the Summer of 2018 as an IBM Extreme Blue intern.</description></item></channel></rss>