<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sharad Shriram</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Sharad Shriram</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:56:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sharadshriram.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Website Update</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/website-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:56:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/website-update/</guid><description>Happy new year, 2022!
Three months into the switch to Hugo, today I was able to add more content about work I have done in the past and improve the access to information aspect of the site. Whilst, the site still needs more content to improve the UX, this is a good start for the new year. The biggest change on the website is on the automation through github actions, whooo!</description></item><item><title>Hugo switch and plans for this blog</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:58:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</guid><description>I have been exploring different static site generators to build my website for a while. The last iteration of this site on https://sharadshriram.github.io was developed on Jekyll where I was tried my hand on understanding the templating language with Jekyll. It was a nice experience where I tried adapting a customized variant of the Read-only theme that was developed by the folks at HTML5up.net.
While I was putting togeher the previous iteration of the site, I had checked out hugo.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/blog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/projects/</guid><description>MyCI: A campus chatbot powered by human-computation (2018) A Telegram-based chatbot developed as a course-project that uses concepts of crowd computing to recommend courses to students from students who have done the same or similar course in the past. Code on Github
Robot Assistant for Cognitively challenged single mothers(2017-18) Using the NAO as robot assistant to assist congitively challenged, single mothers in preparing breakfast. The objective is to give feedback and suggestion on the selected item for breakfast based on whether the item is healthy for the child or not.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</guid><description>An up-to-date list of publications is available on Google Scholar
2021 Athreya, Siva, Giridhara R. Babu, Aniruddha Iyer, Nihesh Rathod, Sharad Shriram, Rajesh Sundaresan, Nidhin Koshy Vaidhiyan, and Sarath Yasodharan. &amp;ldquo;COVID-19: Optimal Design of Serosurveys for Disease Burden Estimation.&amp;rdquo; Sankhya B (2021): 1-23. (author names in alphabetic order) PDF 2020 Talekar, A., Shriram, S., Vaidhiyan, N., Aggarwal, G., Chen, J., Venkatramanan, S., Wang, L., Adiga, A., Sadilek, A.</description></item></channel></rss>