<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sharad Shriram</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sharad Shriram</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:56:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Website Update</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/website-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:56:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/website-update/</guid><description>&lt;p>Happy new year, 2022!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Three months into the switch to Hugo, today I was able to add more content about work I have done in the past and improve the access to information aspect of the site. Whilst, the site still needs more content to improve the UX, this is a good start for the new year. The biggest change on the website is on the automation through github actions, whooo! this was a nice update :D&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hugo switch and plans for this blog</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:58:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/posts/hugo-switch/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have been exploring different static site generators to build my website for a while. The last iteration of this site on &lt;a href="https://sharadshriram.github.io">https://sharadshriram.github.io&lt;/a> was developed on Jekyll where I was tried my hand on understanding the templating language with Jekyll. It was a nice experience where I tried adapting a customized variant of the Read-only theme that was developed by the folks at HTML5up.net.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While I was putting togeher the previous iteration of the site, I had checked out hugo. But the stumble upon was more with the curosity to understand the difference in the time to render the pages between Jekyll and Hugo. But the switch to Hugo is actually motivated by interest to start with Golang. This will be a story for another time, I shall write about how my learning journey goes.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>