<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Sharad Shriram</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Sharad Shriram</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/blog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/blog/</guid><description>I am exploring different ideas to shape my blog post, please staty tuned.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/projects/</guid><description>Archive of all projects I have contributed to over the years that are not part of any published research&amp;hellip;
More projects to be added soon.
2018 MyCI: A campus chatbot powered by human-computation A Telegram-based chatbot developed as a course-project that uses concepts of crowd computing to recommend courses to students from students who have done the same or similar course in the past. Find out more Code Robot Assistant for single mothers with limited cognitive capabilities Using the NAO robot as the assistant to assist congitively challenged, single mothers in preparing breakfast.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/research/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 20:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/page/research/</guid><description>I can also be found on Google Scholar
2021 &amp;nbsp; Siva Athreya, Giridhara R. Babu, Aniruddha Iyer, Nihesh Rathod, Sharad Shriram, Rajesh Sundaresan, Nidhin Koshy Vaidhiyan, and Sarath Yasodharan. COVID-19: Optimal Design of Serosurveys for Disease Burden Estimation, Sankhya B (2021): 1-23. PDF Code 2020 &amp;nbsp; Alok Talekar, Sharad Shriram, Nidhin Vaidhiyan, Gaurav Aggarwal, Jiangzhuo Chen, Srini Venkatramanan, Lijing Wang, Aniruddha Adiga, Adam Sadilek, Ashish Tendulkar, Madhav Marathe, Rajesh Sundaresan, and Milind Tambe.</description></item></channel></rss>